

# **Mohamed Mahmoud**

Address Kankaretie 9 a c 31, 00770 Helsinki

Tel +358 442 08 0939 Email madel413@gmail.com

Profile linkedin.com/in/mohamed-capo

Portfolio capo-portfolio.netlify.app GitHub github.com/capo33

I am a final stage web-development diligent student with 1.5 years of experience a proven knowledge of programming and creating web application. I am highly motivated to continue learning and improving my craft.

# **Software Skills**

Html Css-Sass

Javascript / Angular / React

NodeJS / ExpressJS MySQL / MongoDB

C# / Unity

Basic of Python / PHP Basic of Azure DevOps

#### Skills & Proficiencies

Active listening
Adaptability
Attention to detail
Communication
Customer service

Flexibility

Interpersonal skills

## **Interests & Others**

Gym, football and 3D games B driving license, own car

### Languages

Arabic Mother tongue
English Excellent

Finnish Professional Working Proficiency

# **Educational Background**

### **Encoder training Angular and .Net**

Business College Helsinki Helsinki, Finland 08/2020 - Present

## Hotel, restaurant and catering industry

Varia, Stadin Ammattiopisto Vantaa, Finland 2012 - 2015

#### **Business** management

Higher Institute for Cooperative and administrative Studies Cairo, Egypt

2003 - 2007

# Work Experience

#### The restaurateur, an entrepreneur

Capo33 (Egyptian street food)

06/2019 - 4/2020

## Chef À la carte

La Pasteria Italiana 10/2015 - 8/2019

#### Chef À la carte

Restel Oy

10/2013 - 9/2015